One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Hey, what was that explosion and gunshot?!
What happened to Traf?!
Can you hear me, Luffy?!
What's going on over there?!
Sorry for making a scene.
The pirate and Warlord, Trafalgar Law.
He's the one behind the news this morning about me abdicating the throne.
He tried to force me off the throne.
Don't worry, I've just dealt with him.
So that's what happened.
Dressrosa almost got completely messed up because of him.
Thank goodness!
Hey, Mingo!
How dare you do that to Traf!
Straw Hat, you have no right to condemn me.
Law was originally my subordinate.
I'll be the one to discipline him.
Kin, you carry Traf!
Understood!
Vice Admiral-dono, the Pirate Hunter is attacking. Should we capture him?
Yes.
Wait a moment.
Hey, explain it to us!
What's going on?!
Law-dono has been shot by Doflamingo right before our eyes.
Did you hear that?
The Pirate Hunter and Foxfire Kin'emon...
I saw a kid that looks like Momonosuke on the ship just earlier.
Don't let him get to you.
We won't let him have Momo.
That goes without being said.
He's...
It would seem...
that it'd be better for the both of us if I didn't tell you.
Zoro!
Zoro-dono.
What happened to Zoro, Kin'emon?!
Zoro-dono has disappeared.
Kin'emon!
I'm coming now!
Oh yeah, these were made of Sea Stone.
Kin'emon-san, are you okay?
You haven't been killed, have you?!
Admiral-dono!
A flying slash.
This one's quite strong.
So the blind old gambling man was a Navy Admiral. How about that.
Admiral?!
I thank you for before.
Even though you all helped me out,
it seems I'm repaying you with ingratitude.
This job often brings bad karma.
Oh my, the man with Doflamingo is...
a... a Navy Admiral!
An Admiral is on Dressrosa right now?
It's possible that Doflamingo has allied with the Navy.
If that's the case, then the number of enemies we'll be facing is unknown.
Law-dono! Law-dono!
How are they both flying?!
Are you still alive? Answer me!
We'll continue our talk at the palace, Fujitora.
If you cooperate with me, I'll give you the heads of those brats.
I'll hear you out, Heavenly Demon.
But I'll decide what to do after that.
Capture Roronoa Zoro!
Looks like they know who we are.
So it would seem.
So for now, let's run!
Traf!
This is Kin'emon, Law-dono has been taken by them!
Hey Luffy, hurry and find an exit!
We'll keep running around here and wait for you!
Alright, I'll hurry.
I can still sense Traf. He's alive.
It's Brook and the others.
What's going on now?
T-T-T-This...
What's going on on the Sunny?
They were behind us!
Dammit, they found us.
This is bad!
It's Big Mom's...
... pirate ship!
Ship, ship♪
What is the ship of one of the Four Emperors doing here?!
Is the prow singing?
Really?!
Big Mom's ship?!
We're gonna die!
What's going on, is Big Mom on that ship?
I don't know, but those two we met on Fishman Island are onboard.
Mama, I've spotted Caesar -gao!
As we thought, he was with them -bon.
We should sink their ship and pull Caesar up -soir.
Big Mom?!
I told you so.
This is because you picked a fight with her, Luffy!
They seem to be after Caesar.
You're really popular aren't you, evil scientist!
Is that ship here to save you as well?!
Save me please!
You can't let Big Mom capture me!
I got my research funds...
by tricking her and ripping her off!
What did you say?
W-Well... let's not talk about the details!
Anyway if I'm captured, they'll find out that I've stolen the money and kill me!
Like I care about your life!
Well, I can't let them take you anyway, so shut up!
They're gonna shoot at us!
Damn, we're getting farther away from Dressrosa. They couldn't have picked a worse time to appear!
Can you lose them?
Are you okay, Sanji?
Don't you dare bring an Emperor to this country.
This whole country would fall into panic and the soldier's plans will be screwed.
By the way, why is Caesar on the ship?
I guess negotiations have broken down.
Why else would Traf end up like that?
Law told us to take Caesar to the next island, that's why he's here.
Sanji-kun, I don't think we should go back to Dressrosa.
I'm not saying this because I'm scared.
Listen, Luffy.
We have three cards that we're competing with Doflamingo for.
Caesar, the Smile factory, and for some reason, Momonosuke.
We still haven't destroyed the Smile factory.
But we have the other two cards right here.
Traf fought because he was a decoy to lure Doflamingo away from these cards.
He may also be trying to buy time to destroy the factory.
If we go there and give up the cards that Traf tried so hard to protect...
All his hard work will be in vain.
You're right.
Alright, we'll definitely get Traf back!
What was the next island called?
It's called Zou.
Sanji.
Nami.
Chopper.
Brook.
Momo.
You guys, go on ahead to Zou.
If you say so... Roger, Captain!
But I'd like your permission for something.
Permission?
Allow me...
to attack Big Mom's ship!
Yeah, sure.
You're joking.
We've already picked a fight with her.
You got that right.
That's too dangerous!
Please stop!
Alright, we'll be waiting for you guys on Zou.
Got it.
Leave the destruction of the factory to us!
Everyone, be careful.
We're heading to the palace.
We're gonna send Doflamingo flying!
Barrier!
What is the meaning of this?!
Bartolomeo?
This has nothing to do with you!
True. I just felt like raising this barrier.
This is a family matter! I'll kill you too!
Just try. Nobody can break my barrier.
What? I'm busy!
It's me, Dellinger.
Sounds like you still haven't finished off Bellamy.
You slowpoke.
Oh, shut up! Something got in the way.
Never mind, we'll deal with that later.
Doffy has a new order for you.
Go help Lao G and the others protect the Toys' House. Right now.
Wait, Diamante! I'll be done here in a second!
Be quiet! Do you plan to disobey Doffy?!
"A new order"?
So I...
really was...
You gotta be kidding...
Get real!
Get out of my way.
I'm going... to kick Bellamy to death!
Move it!
No way. I ain't removing the barrier.
I heard that call just now.
So get out of here!
Damn barrier-bastard!
I'll get you for this!
You're not leaving Dressrosa alive!
Scram, you little brat!
That was Diamante's voice, no doubt about it.
So that order was for real?
Doflamingo really did...
order my death?
So if I win this tournament, I'll become a commander in the Family?
Of course.
Do your best.
I've got high hopes for you.
I'll take you to the medical room.
I don't need your help!
I've lost my goal in life.
And anyway, why would you help me?
In the battle royale earlier...
I was trying to kill all of you guys!
We fought in the same ring!
What?
When two men have exchanged blows on the battlefield,
that makes them comrades in arms!
I'd never abandon a comrade, no matter how rotten he may be!
Dressrosa "Flower Hill"
The situation is like I explained.
As for our plan to expose the tragedies
Underground - Riku's Revolutionary Army Base
that have been buried in the darkness,
I've given it the following name.
The Dressrosa SOP Operation.
SOP? What's that mean?
There is a massive underground world in this country.
Inside is the trade port, for making secret deals,
as well as the mysterious factory.
Our Tontattan friends
Factory & trade port
and all the people turned into toys
are being forced to work there.
I see! So what does SOP mean?
We will break in there using the tunnel we've spent the last year digging,
Secretly infiltrate
via tunnel
and rescue everyone there!
Then we will destroy the facilities, take down the Doflamingo Family, and restore King Riku!
That is the objective of our plan.
You talk as if it's gonna be easy.
Of course, the plan is extremely idealistic.
We have no idea what will happen to Dressrosa in the next few minutes.
First and foremost, there is one mission we absolutely must carry out.
Doflamingo's subordinate, the one who turned us into toys...
We must knock the Hobby Fruit user unconscious!
Hobby Fruit?
What do you think will happen then?
Will the spell be broken?
That's right! All the toys in Dressrosa...
will return to human form at once!
At the same time, the people will regain whatever memories they have lost.
We can't guess what will happen after that.
Not how many people will fight alongside us, nor what the people will think, nor what actions they'll take.
Or what move Doflamingo will make.
What move the Navy will make.
The only thing we can say for sure,
is that panic will erupt throughout the country.
So, where is this Hobby Fruit user?
And he's really strong, right?
According to the Tontatta reconnaissance unit,
she's in the trade port right now.
She is a special commander in the Donquixote Family's Trébol Army.
Sugar!
A girl who can turn anyone she touches into a toy.
She looks like a child, because whoever eats this fruit stops aging once they do.
She is regarded as one of Doflamingo's most valuable subordinates,
so one of his top commanders, Trébol, is guarding her at all times.
So if we can just make her fall unconscious, the toys will return to normal?
Indeed!
We will scare Sugar half to death and make her faint.
That is the...
Sugar
Sugar Oversurprise
Sugar Oversurprise Panic Operation!
I combined the first letters from each of those words to form the name SOP.
That's a great operation name!
If the enemy is just a little girl, then you can leave this to me!
Alright, I'm fired up!
Franky Hair Salon!
Battle-Hair!
Fraland!
Usoland!
You're so dependable!
Indeed! We are here for you!
There's no way we can lose this battle!
Take us to the underground passage, little ones!
Usolanders!
Meanwhile, Luffy was searching for the exit to the Corrida Colosseum.
Huh?
I don't see any exits.
Where am I?
Someday, I will work under Luffy-senpai.
That's my dream.
You could at least close the door again!
The toilet?
Oh, you're the hen-comb guy!
I'm so glad to see you!
L-L-Luffy-senpai!
No!
Keep it together, Bartolomeo!
Do you really want to give up the chance to speak with the Pirate King?
Oh, Bellamy.
Damn it! He's shining too brightly, I can't look him in the eyes!
Luffy-senpai!
Did you manage to meet up with Zoro-senpai?
Yeah, I talked to him. Thanks!
Oh, it was nothing!
So I suddenly have something I need to do, so I've gotta leave...
but I can't find the exit.
This colosseum doesn't have an exit.
Huh?
Is it just me...
or have your injuries gotten worse?
Once a fighter enters the colosseum, they can never leave.
You're wasting your time looking for an exit.
What? What do you mean?
For real?
There really isn't one?!
Aren't you supposed to be Doflamingo's underling?
So you've gotta know something!
His underling? I couldn't even become that!
Please! My friend is in danger!
I'm leaving.
If you follow me, you might be able to get out too... Maybe.
Alright, thanks!
You'll take me out?
All I'm saying is, you might make it out by coincidence if you follow me.
You want me to betray my boss?
I...
can't betray Doflamingo!
I have too much respect for him.
Hey, didn't he just...
Shut up!
I have my own morals I must stick to.
Got it. I'll tag along behind you then.
But then, Luffy-senpai...
What about the Flame Fruit?
There's someone I really don't want to have it, but I've got no choice.
My friends' lives are more important.
Don't worry, I'll handle it!
It's a memento of Ace-sama. I was always planning to give it to you, Luffy-senpai!
Huh? You'll give it to me?
Of course! If anyone should have it, it's you!
Your accent keep getting heavier.
Ah'll definitely get ya the Flame Fruit!
Just go do whatever it was ya needed to do!
Who are you talking to?
Alright, that really helps.
I won't let you have the Flame Fruit...
Straw Hat Luffy.
Who're you?
Why're you just casually talking to Luffy-senpai like that?
He is the younger brother of that legendary pirate Fire Fist Ace-sama,
and the future Pirate King, you dumbass!
I've known that for a long time.
Now the real battle starts!
You'd better make it to the final round!
Sure!
What's he doing? How dare he act all chummy with Luffy-senpai?!
See? He got him mad!
The plaza outside the Corrida Colosseum
Why'd you come out crying?!
You couldn't find the Pirate Hunter?!
Didn't I tell you to keep your guard up?!
Call the Vice-Admiral!
Yes, Sir!
The Navy has completely fallen for our disguise. They believe us to be toys.
This is still cutting it too close!
And why'd you choose these specific animals?
I thought these animals were kewl! Especially, carps?
Oh, shut up you! Do you even want to save Traf?!
We'll save Traf! I'll send Mingo flying!
And we don't have to worry about the Flame Fruit either.
But are you okay?
It seems Robin-san is somewhere in this country too.
I'd really like to see her again.
Revolutionary Army - Fishman Karate assistant instructor
Koala
I'm glad you got to meet up with your friend.
Yeah... I thought he was going to hit me.
Are you crying?
As if!
Could you have made a difference if you were there?
Nobody can say for sure.
You're right.
Once you've figured out what's happening underground, tell me.
Of course.
In any case, I will get Ace's Flame Fruit.
We will carry on his will!
I did't thing he waz alive...
Who are you talking about?!
I thought...
h-h-he...
The Straw Hats are Back
he died back then!